Guide to the New York City Central Labor Council Photographs PHOTOS 020
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
New York City Central Labor Council Photographs
1940-1997, bulk 1970-1989
1970-1989
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
AFL-CIO. New York City Central Labor Council
PHOTOS 020
15.25 Linear Feet in 21 manuscript containers, 6 record cartons, and 3 folders.
The Central Trades and Labor Council of the American Federation of Labor merged with the New York City Congress of Industrial Organizations Council on February 19, 1959 to form the New York City Central Labor Council, AFL-CIO. The Council is an organization comprised of nearly 400 local union affiliates. The collection consists of approximately 8,200 mostly 8x10 black and white glossy prints, spanning the 1940s through the late 1990s, with the bulk dating from the 1970s and 1980s. Major areas covered by the collection include demonstrations by Council affiliates on various issues, and annual Council activities and events, such as the New York City Labor Day Parade. The principal photographers are Sam Reiss, Alexander Archer, Dan Miller, Jules Geller, and Mildred Gross.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by the New York City Central Labor Council in several installments beginning in 1986. The accession numbers associated with these donations are 1986.041, 1986.036, and 2011.093. Additionally, sixty color photographs from the 1991 Labor Day Parade were donated by Brian McLaughlin from the Central Labor Council in 1996. The accession number associated with this gift is NPA.2001.008.
Arrangement
The New York City Central Labor Council Photographs are arranged into fourteen series, several of which are further arranged into subseries and sub-subseries.
The series arrangement is as follows:
Series I. Organization
Subseries IA. History and Predecessor Organizations
Subseries IB. Central Labor Council Elections
Subseries IC. Central Labor Council General
Sub-subseries IC1. Executive Board
Sub-subseries IC2. Other
Subseries ID. Committees
Sub-subseries ID1. Black Trade Unionists Labor Committee
Sub-subseries ID2. Hispanic Labor Committee
Sub-subseries ID3. Interium Organization
Sub-subseries ID4. Non-Partisan (Borough and County)
Subseries IE. Conventions
Sub-subseries IE1. AFL-CIO
Sub-subseries IE2. New York State AFL-CIO
Subseries IF. Conferences
Subseries IG. Delegates
Series II. Affiliates
Series III. Services
Subseries IIIA. Educational Programs
Sub-subseries IIIA1. School of Industrial and Labor Relations
Sub-subseries IIIA2. Empire State College
Sub-subseries IIIA3. Wagner Summer School
Subseries IIIB. Camps
Subseries IIIC. Social Services/Community Services
Series IV. Events
Subseries IVA. Central Labor Council Annual Events
Sub-subseries IVA1. Community
Sub-subseries IVA2. Conference - Civil Rights
Sub-subseries IVA3. Labor Day Mass
Sub-subseries IVA4. Labor Day Street Fair
Sub-subseries IVA5. Martin Lacey Scholarship
Sub-subseries IVA6. Lincoln's Birthday Dinne r
Sub-subseries IVA7. Workers Memorial Day
Subseries IVB. Awards
Series V. Chronological
Series VI. Portraits and Individuals
Series VII. Parades
Subseries VIIA. Easter
Subseries VIIB. Labor Day
Subseries VIIC. May Day
Subseries VIID. St. Patrick's Day
Subseries VIIE. Solidarity Day
Series VIII. Demonstrations
Series IX. Electoral Politics
Subseries IXA. Voter Registration
Subseries IXB. Election Campaigns
Series X. Community Services
Series XI. Other Organizations
Series XII. Copy Negatives
Series XIII. Oversized Prints
Series XIV. Unprocessed
Folders are arranged chronologically within each series and subseries.
Historical/Biographical Note
The Central Trades and Labor Council of the American Federation of Labor merged with the New York City Congress of Industrial Organizations Council on February 19, 1959 to form the New York City Central Labor Council, AFL-CIO. This followed the earlier merger on December 9, 1958 of New York State's AFL and CIO.
The New York City Central Labor Council is an organization comprised of nearly 400 local union affiliates. It acts only on local activities and concerns and it does not issue statements on AFL-CIO policy. According to its constitution, the council's purpose is to further the rights of workers to organize in unions and to bargain collectively, to advocate legislation which is beneficial to workers and oppose that which is not, and to correct abuses and to insure the workers their just rights.
The New York City Central Labor Council also has social and political purposes driven by the commitment to help all people who work for a living improve their working conditions and raise their standard of living. Further, the New York City Central Labor Council strives to preserve workers' rights to act together for mutual aid and advancement, to further the cause of unions, and to strengthen civil rights. It acts as a central force, providing assistance and education through its various committees and councils.
The regular activities of the New York City Central Labor Council are directed by its executive officers, Executive Board, and Delegates' Council meetings. The planning and execution of programs and conferences are conducted by various standing and special committees. These committees are composed of members from affiliated local unions, each with officers and advisory consulting staff. An important special committee is the Labor Day Parade Committee.
In 1957, Harry Van Arsdale was elected president of the Central Trades and Labor Council of the AFL. Following the merger in 1959, he became the President of the Central Labor Council. During his presidency (1957-1986), the council established many diverse committees and programs such as the Rehabilitation Council (1963), Hispanic Labor Committee (1970), and the Black Trade Unionist Leadership Committee (1972). The Council was also instrumental in founding the Harry Van Arsdale Jr. Center for Labor Studies, in 1971, to further labor education at Empire State College, State University of New York.
Upon Harry Van Arsdale's death in 1986, his son, Thomas Van Arsdale, was elected to the post of president.
Related Material at the Tamiment Library/Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
New York City Central Labor Council Collection (WAG 049)
Scope and Content Note
The collection consists of approximately 8,200 photographs, most of which are 8x10 black and white glossy prints. Many were shot for potential use in Labor Chronicle, the Council's newspaper (published between the 1960s and early 1980s), and other Council publications.
The images span the 1940s through the late 1990s, although the bulk of the photographs date from the 1970s and 1980s. Particularly well documented are Council special committees; demonstrations by Council affiliates; and annual Council activities and events, such as the New York City Labor Day Parade and Lincoln Birthday Dinner.
Prominent individuals are also well-represented, both in portraits and group shots. These include the presidents of the various locals represented on the Council, Executive Board members, and the officers of the Council. The officers most well documented are: Harry Van Arsdale, President; Harry Avrutin, Secretary; Morris Iushewitz, Secretary (Avrutin's immediate predecessor); and William Bowe, Treasurer.
The collection also includes numerous photographs of many major New York City and New York State political figures and office-holders from the 1940s and onwards, shown posed with Council members or other labor leaders. Notable inclusions are mayors Robert F. Wagner, Jr., Abraham Beame, Edward Koch, Rudolph Giuliani, and Governors Mario Cuomo and George Pataki.
The principal photographers in this collection are: Sam Reiss, Alexander Archer, Dan Miller, Jules Geller, and Mildred Gross; their credit lines may be seen stamped on the back of many of the images.
Labor union meetings |v Pictorial works.; Labor unions |x Congresses and conventions |v portraits.; Labor Day |v Pictorial works.; Demonstrations |z New York (State) |z New York |v Pictorial works.; Black-and-white negatives.; Collective bargaining.; Labor leaders |z New York (State) |z New York |v Portraits.; Labor unions |x Political activity |x Law and legislation.; Industrial hygiene |x Law and legislation.; Mediation and conciliation, Industrial |z New York (State) |z New York.; Labor union members |z United States.; New York (N.Y.); Photographic prints.; Black-and-white photographs.; Avrutin, Harry; Bowe, William--Portraits.; Archer, Alexander; Geller, Jules.; Labor chronicle; Gross, Mildred.; Iushewitz, Morris. -- |v Portraits; Miller, Dan.; Van Arsdale, Harry, 1905-1986 -- |v Portraits; Reiss, Sam
- Series I: Organization, circa 1950-1986
  Scope and Content Note
  Series I: Organization, circa 1950-1986, documents the history of the New York City Central Labor Council, its predecessor organizations, Council elections, Council committees, in addition to affiliated conventions and conferences. The Black Trade Unionists Leadership Committee and the Hispanic Labor Committee are well documented in this series.
  - Subseries A: History and Predecessor Organizations
    - C.I.O. New York City Council, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Council Merger, Jan 13, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Subseries B: Central Labor Council Elections
    - Installation of Officers [New York City Council], Dec 16, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Swearing in, Dec 20, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Elections, Mar 20, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Subseries C: Central Labor Council General
    - Sub-Subseries 1) Executive Board
      - Executive Board Meeting, Mar 18, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Executive Board Meeting, Jul 13, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Executive Board Meeting, Sep 21, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Executive Board Meeting, Sep 20, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Executive Board Meeting, Jan 17, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Executive Board Meeting, Apr 18, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Executive Board Meeting, Dec 19, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Executive Board Meeting, Mar 26, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Executive Board Meeting, Aug 1975 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Executive Board Meeting, Nov 20, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Executive Board Meeting, Sep 16, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Executive Board Meeting, Dec 16, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Executive Board Meeting, May 19, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Executive Board Meeting, Aug 17, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Executive Board Meeting, Dec 21, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - Executive Board Meeting, Jul 19, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Executive Board Meeting, Nov 20, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - Executive Board Meeting, Apr 16, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - Executive Board Meeting, May 6, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Sub-Subseries 2) Other
      - Meetings: General, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
      - Advisory Council: Labor College Meeting, Jun 14, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 26)
      - Advisory Council, Sep 7, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 27)
      - Advisory Council Meeting, Feb 1980 (Box 1, Folder 28)
      - Census Meeting, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 29)
      - Community Service Committee Meeting, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 30)
      - Community Service Committee Meeting, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      - Jobs for Youth, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 32)
      - Manpower Committee Meeting, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - Save Our Schools Ad Hoc Committee, May 1, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 34)
      - Shorter Work Week Committee, circa 1950, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Subseries D: Committees
    - Sub-Subseries 1) Black Trade Unionists Labor Committee
      - Black Trade Unionists Leaders Committee, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 36)
      - Black Trade Unionists Leaders Committee: Dinner, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 37)
      - Black Trade Unionists Leaders Committee: Dinner, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 38)
      - Black Trade Unionists Leaders Committee: Dinner, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 39)
      - Black Trade Unionists Leaders Committee: Dinner, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 40)
      - Black Trade Unionists Leaders Committee: Dinner, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 41)
      - Black Trade Unionists Leaders Committee: Dinner, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Sub-Subseries 2) Hispanic Labor Committee
      - Hispanic Labor Committee: Awards, undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
      - Hispanic Labor Committee: Conference, undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
      - Spanish Labor Committee Meeting, Feb 5, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 45)
      - Hispanic Labor Committee: Dinner, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 46)
      - Hispanic Labor Committee: [Dinner], Jan 11, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 47)
      - Hispanic Labor Committee Endorses Governor Hugh Carey, Oct 26, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 48)
      - Hispanic Labor Committee Conference, Apr 16, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 49)
      - Hispanic Labor Committee: Dinner, Dec 18, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 50)
      - Hispanic Labor Committee: Dinner, Dec 2, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 51)
      - Hispanic Labor Committee: Dinner, Nov 24, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Sub-Subseries 3) Interim Organization
      - Interim Organization, Dec 27, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 53)
      - Interim Organization: Steering Committee, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Sub-Subseries 4) Non-Partisan (Borough and County)
      - Unidentified, circa 1969 - 1979, undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
      - Non-Partisan Borough Committee, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 56)
      - Non-Partisan Borough Committee Elections, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 57)
      - Non-Partisan Five County Committee, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 58)
      - Non-Partisan Five County Committee, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 59)
      - Non-Partisan Five County Committee, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 60)
      - Non-Partisan Five County Committee, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Subseries E: Conventions
    - Sub-Subseries 1) AFL-CIO
      - Convention: AFL/CIO, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 62)
      - Convention: AFL/CIO, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 63)
      - Convention: AFL/CIO, Nov 22, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 64)
      - Convention: AFL/CIO, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 65)
      - Convention: AFL/CIO, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 66)
      - Convention: AFL/CIO, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Sub-Subseries 2) New York State AFL-CIO
      - Convention, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 68)
      - Convention, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Subseries F: Conferences
    - Conferences: General, undated (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Conference: Unemployment, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Conference: Education, May 21, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Conference: Drug Abuse, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Conference: Imports, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Conference: National Health Insurance, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Conference: Payable Tax, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Conference: United Italian-American Labor Council, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Conference: International Affairs, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Conference: New York Women's Trade Union, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Conference: Help for Unemployed, Mar 21, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Conference: Education, Aug 10, 1978-Aug 13, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Conference: Jewish Labor Committee, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Conference: Education, Jun 9, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Conference: Roosevelt Centenary, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Subseries G: Delegates
    - Delegates Meeting, undated (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Delegates Meeting, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Delegates Meeting, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Delegates Meeting, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Delegates Meeting, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - Delegates Meeting, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Delegates Meeting: Visit Council Headquarters, undated (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Delegates Meeting: Visit Council Headquarters, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 92)
- Series II: Affiliates, 1965-1977
  Series II: Affiliates, 1965-1977, contains photographs of organizations with whom the New York City Central Labor Council collaborated over a period of twelve years. This series includes photographic documentation of Actors Equity and the Transport Workers Union, among others.
  - Affiliates General, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Convention: Council Supervisors and Administrators (AFL-CIO), 1972 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Actors Equity: Hearing, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Transport Workers Union: Local 100 Membership Meeting, Mar 1973 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Scholarship: Local 23-25, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 97)
- Series III: Services, 1964-1982
  Series III: Services, 1964-1982, documents various enrichment programs which were either led by the New York City Central Labor Council or developed out of collaboration with other institutions. This series contains photographs of educational programs, camps, as well as social and community services.
  - Subseries A: Educational Programs
    - Sub-Subseries 1) School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Cornell University, undated
      - Risley's Class Visits Central Labor Council, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 98)
      - Risley's Class Visits Central Labor Council, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - Sub-Subseries 2) Empire State College
      - Empire College, undated (Box 3, Folder 100)
      - Labor College, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 101)
      - Labor College, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 102)
      - Labor College: Collective Bargaining Class, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 103)
      - Labor College Dinner, May 1975 (Box 3, Folder 104)
      - Labor College Dinner, Sep 1976 (Box 3, Folder 105)
      - Labor College: Graduation (1st), Sep 3, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 106)
      - Labor College: Graduation, Sep 6, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 107)
      - Labor College: Graduation, Jun 25, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 108)
      - Labor College: Graduation, Jun 24, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 109)
      - Labor College: Graduation, Jun 13, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 110)
      - Labor College: Graduation, Jun 25, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 111)
      - Labor College: Scholarship and Award Ceremony, Dec 1, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Sub-Subseries 3) Wagner Summer School
      - Wagner Summer School, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 113)
      - Wagner Summer School, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 114)
      - Wagner Summer School, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Subseries B: Camps
    - Camp Sebago, undated (Box 4, Folder 116)
    - Camp Wabenaki, undated (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Subseries C: Social Services/Community Services
    - Performing Arts and Cultural Project, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 118)
    - Red Cross Labor Seminar, May 1975 (Box 4, Folder 119)
    - Red Cross Labor Seminar, May 1977 (Box 4, Folder 120)
- Series IV: Events, 1963-1991
  Series IV: Events, 1963-1982, contains photographs of annual New York City Central Labor Council events and distributed awards. Areas of strength include documentation of the Council's Community Service Institute and Civil Rights Conference, in addition to more prominent occasions such as the Labor Day Street Fair and Abraham Lincoln Birthday Dinner. Awards distributed on behalf of the Council are also well documented in this series.
  - Subseries A: Central Labor Council Annual Events
    - Sub-Subseries 1) Community
      - Community Service Institute, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 121)
      - Community Service Institute, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 122)
      - Community Service Institute, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 123)
      - Community Service Institute, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 124)
      - Community Service Institute, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 125)
      - Community Service Institute, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 126)
      - Community Service Institute, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 127)
      - Community Service Institute, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 128)
      - Community Service Institute, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 129)
      - Community Service Institute, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - Sub-Subseries 2) Conference—Civil Rights
      - Conference: Civil Rights, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 131)
      - Conference: Civil Rights, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 132)
      - Conference: Civil Rights, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 133)
      - Conference: Civil Rights, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 134)
    - Sub-Subseries 3) Labor Day Mass
      - Labor Day Mass: St. Patrick's Cathedral, Sep 6, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 135)
      - Labor Day Mass, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 136)
      - Labor Day Mass, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 137)
      - Labor Day Mass, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 138)
      - Labor Day Mass, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 139)
      - Labor Day Mass, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 140)
      - Labor Day Mass, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - Sub-Subseries 4) Labor Day Street Fair
      - Labor Day Street Fair, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - Sub-Subseries 5) Martin Lacey Scholarship
      - Lacey, Martin: Scholarship, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 143)
      - Lacey, Martin: Scholarship, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 144)
      - Lacey, Martin: Scholarship, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 145)
      - Lacey, Martin: Scholarship, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 146)
      - Lacey, Martin: Scholarship, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - Sub-Subseries 6) Lincoln's Birthday Dinner
      - Lincoln's Birthday Dinner, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 148)
      - Lincoln's Birthday Dinner, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 149)
      - Lincoln's Birthday Dinner, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 150)
      - Lincoln's Birthday Dinner, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 151)
      - Lincoln's Birthday Dinner, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 152)
      - Lincoln's Birthday Dinner, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 153)
      - Lincoln's Birthday Dinner, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 154)
      - Lincoln's Birthday Dinner, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 155)
      - Lincoln's Birthday Dinner, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 156)
      - Lincoln's Birthday Dinner, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 157)
      - Lincoln's Birthday Dinner, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 158)
      - Lincoln's Birthday Dinner, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 159)
      - Lincoln's Birthday Dinner, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 160)
      - Lincoln's Birthday Dinner, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 161)
      - Lincoln's Birthday Dinner, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 162)
      - Lincoln's Birthday Dinner, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 163)
      - Lincoln's Birthday Dinner, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 164)
      - Lincoln's Birthday Dinner, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 165)
      - Lincoln's Birthday Dinner, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 166)
      - Lincoln's Birthday Dinner, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 167)
      - Lincoln's Birthday Dinner, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 168)
      - Lincoln's Birthday Dinner, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 169)
      - Lincoln's Birthday Dinner, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 170)
    - Sub-Subseries 7) Workers Memorial Day
      - Third Annual Workers Memorial Day, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 171)
  - Subseries B: Awards
    - Awards: General, undated (Box 6, Folder 172)
    - David Dubinsky Week, Oct 12, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 173)
    - Dan, Dr. Phan Quang: Reception, May 22, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 174)
    - Israel's 20th Anniversary, Jun 11, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 175)
    - Bowe Dinner, Jun 12, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 176)
    - Campaign: United States Savings Bond, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 177)
    - Diehl Dinner, Jun 12, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 178)
    - Meany Dinner: Irish Historical Society, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 179)
    - Plunkett, Chris: Bon Voyage to Israel, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 180)
    - Israel United, Nov 1973 (Box 6, Folder 181)
    - Service Employees Dinner, 1973, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 182)
    - Burnell: Swearing In, Jan 29, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 183)
    - Senate Hearing on Unemployment, Mar 1975 (Box 6, Folder 184)
    - Drug Abuse Press Conference, May 1975 (Box 6, Folder 185)
    - "Collective Bargaining" George Segal, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 186)
    - Contract for Job Placement Program, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 187)
    - [Bicentennial Event], 1976 (Box 6, Folder 188)
    - Bicentennial Event: Entertainment: "I Paid My Dues", 1976 (Box 6, Folder 189)
    - Meany Award, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 190)
    - Jewish Labor Committee Dinner, Jan 12, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 191)
    - Burnell Installation, Mar 1, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 192)
    - Lewis Hine Photo Exhibition, Mar. 1977-May 1977 (Box 6, Folder 193)
    - Bukovsky Luncheon, Dec 10, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 194)
    - Testimonial Dinner Honoring Reverend Philip A. Carey, Nov 15, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 195)
    - Taiwanese Delegation, Jul 19, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 196)